Just kidding. Oh, good. It's not that.
It's not that. It's just feminist.
I'm recording, so whenever you want, go for it.
Hi calls
Portland. I was at a cafe this morning, and a girl talked like that,
and I looked over, and it was like a grown woman, and I was like,
Stop talking. Well, apparently that's
fine. Apparently the line in Tyler Swift's song is, like, I used to know
if I feel like everyone's a sexy baby is her commenting
on women who help
me. I'm a baby. Also, you're doing a lot of stone damage to
her vocal cords. What if that was my sexy baby?
My sexy baby? It's just like I sound like I'm dying. Somebody's got a
piano string around your neck. Hey,
fuckers. How you doing? How you been? You good? You're all right? You're hanging in
there? Well, welcome to another episode of Guys we effect.
It's the anti flutching podcast. I'm corrine Fischer.
Christina Hutchinson. Welcome to the goddamn show. Here.
We're here. Let's get into it. Let's read an email.
Do you want to read this, or do you want me to? Sure, I'll read
if you want. You can read it. I couldn't be my boyfriend's
dead mom, and he made it my fault. It sounds
like it was your fault. What a title. Wait. I couldn't be my boyfriend's dead
mom, and he made it my fault? Okay.
Another stellar gentleman making an appearance. Hi, guys. I really love
the show. I've been listening for years, and I know I'm better for it.
I still have some dumb bitch in me, though. We all do.
My ex and I broke up this week. He 30, lost his mom a year
and a half ago, and he won't stop yapping.
My mom died because this is
not triggering because of my last breakup. She had
been sick for a long time. We started dating about six months after she
passed, and that's called too soon. Learn that the hard way.
I'm 24 and feel like this was the first relationship I really put
my all into. He got time. Yeah. I mean, you're making a little bit
about, yo, I have a man you
could call. I have a friend who you
could text. He expressed early on that
he wanted more from me, and I stepped up as much as I could.
Like, anal or, like, emotional. So probably emotional. Probably not analy.
Yeah. I got to say no. And there
was no stage of grief where I was like, I want it up the butt.
All the holes are nothing.
I was vulnerable and sensitive to what he's going through.
I mean, his mom died. I'm guessing that you were vulnerable
and sensitive in the way that, again, so ironic.
Only a 24 year old could be, which is not a lot
for the people in the back of the room, because we're talking about therapy
for weeks. It's not a lot. So that one more year development.
Oh, God. Okay.
I told him everything. That's not helpful when you're going through death.
So, anyway, about me, you know what I loved? When?
Right after my dad's died, just a long story about my boyfriend day at
work. That was really helpful.
I told him everything. He's the first person I opened up to about so many
things, and he listened. So compassionately and respectfully.
Honestly shocking, considering the death of his mother was only six months prior.
Maybe it was just my first adult relationship, but the emotional connection and trust I
felt with him was like nothing I've ever had. And I'm scared I won't have
it again. Girl, you're 24. Yeah, to buy that
at the supermarket. Over the course of our relationship,
more things happen with his family. His brother and him had a falling out,
and then his brother was committed to a mental hospital,
and then his dad started romantically dating his dead
mom's sister. That's a lot of lairs. We should be more respectful
to you, actually. Shit, that's a lot.
Drama. That's a lot. Drama. That's a lot.
I need a button that says drama. I can just see her being like,
god, my boyfriend should just get a tattoo on his wrist that says, I hate
drama because he loves it. Drama in my life.
Honestly, I'm not sure if anyone can take any
of that well. But he struggled and had a hard time letting me
support him. Plus, I had a hard time knowing how to support him.
And I feel you on that, because I would be like, don't talk to me.
And then I'd be like, I open talks. That would
be confusing. Leave me alone,
but come over.
That's the scales of the libra. That's what they're talking about. One side is
saying, Leave me alone. And one side is saying, Come over. Well, what you say
and what you want, two different things. He is looking
for what makes him happy. He feels like he cannot continue living like he
is working in the city, living in Brooklyn. Brooklyn difficult.
I know that subway. Going out with friends. Basically how most normal
people live in NYC. In hindsight, the relationship should have ended sooner.
It probably shouldn't have even started. Oh, boy.
I wasn't getting what I needed. I was exhausting myself trying
to give what he needed, and it still wasn't enough for him. When he's not
making this up, this is actually what the reader wrote us. The writer wrote us
when he initiated the breakup last week. He said, you don't feel like home to
me. I don't think he really has a home right now. Speaking of liberty's
on the tone, though, we don't know.
His family is so fucked up, and he's trying to fill that void with a
relationship. That's every relationship that I've ever been in. I mean, not on
my end, but done with the other person, sure. But no, he's not.
He's dedumped you. So is he trying to fill the void with the relationship?
Did he dump, or did they break out? I thought you don't feel like home
to me. I mean, that's me. Oh, right, right. Oh, he initiated it.
He initiated. Okay. Yes. So I don't think you're trying
to fill the void with the relationship. He dumped you. If he was doing that,
he would be more codependent with you. Seems like he was traumatized, and he was
like, I'm gonna traumatize this bitch by having her go through the first breakup
she's ever been through. We're all playing hot potato with our pain, guys.
Oh, man. His family is so fucked up. He's trying to follow the void with
our relationship. Shortly before the breakup, my dad was diagnosed with cancer.
Wow. You guys can't have a moment to this guy by himself.
It's been really difficult, but my ex relates to it, and I was a yes,
of course. Also, God, I feel like this is,
like, such kismet, because this feels to me, like, universally,
it's like you kind of, like, didn't get the pain your boyfriend
was going through, and now that God saying, like, you're about
to know first hand, isn't life sick?
It's been really difficult, but my ex relates to it, and that was such a
blessing. Now the relationship is over, and I am so heartbroken.
You just said it shouldn't have started. What? Pick one.
He says he wants to still support me, but I don't think I'm strong
enough to have him in my life. It's too much. I'm worried
leaning on him will hurt too much while I'll start to get too hopeful
about a reconciliation of a relationship you didn't think should begin with in the first
place. Right. But also, it's a very isolating experience. For sure.
It is. But you can leave on your house and the rest of your family
in this time. Also, I think it's
a little bit of a young person, not a young person.
I don't know. I'm weird with family and relationships
because it always bothers me. I guess it depends on the
relationship with your family. So I have a good relationship with my family, so I
lean on my family during times like this because it's a family issue.
If you have a good relationship with your family, but instead you're choosing
to lean on a boyfriend who are not even that close with to me,
that's strange. Yeah. And it seems like going away a little bit, and you're taking
time away where you can be connecting with your father during this. I'm sure he's
freaked out too, probably more than you are, because he's the one with
cancer. Right, right. And obviously things can be fun. I know lots of
people who have parents had to have cancer. Turned out totally fine, for sure.
But he needs support of his family. And again, like Rin said,
I don't know if you have a good relationship with her or not. If it's
toxic, if it's not good, that adds a layer to it. But I think you
can use a hug. Your dad also, like, the good news is,
honestly, if you're heartbroken about this breakup, great timing,
because nothing takes your mind off a breakup like your dad being very
ill. Oh, my God. Honestly,
this is so crazy to say, but I mean it from the bottom of
my heart. Hey, girl. It was so what a relief to
think about and be sad over a man that I was
not romantically involved with. Fucking freedom.
Wow. It was devastating. I still cry about it to this day.
I will never be the same person, but, God damn, was it nice
for at age 35 to finally be sad over a guy
who I had not fucked. It was great.
I guess my question is just how to deal. I've never felt more alone,
and I know the relationship had to end, and knowing that helps, but it hurts
again. Love you guys. Love the show. Never stop what you're doing. I think you
just have to experience the hurts, and then it
won't hurt after time happens.
That's, like, exactly how this goes. And it's your first
relationship, so you don't know this yet, and that's okay,
but that's what happens. You mourn the relationship. You grieve
it, and you allow yourself to grieve it. Cry if
you want to cry. Spend time on the couch. Bingewise.
Don't give yourself too long because you don't want to get lost in this,
like, well of grief and never come out. That's not going to be beneficial
for you. But allow yourself to grieve this relationship. Remind yourself that
you just told us you didn't even know if you wanted it to begin in
the first place. So while you're grieving, also go, hey, you know
what, girl? This isn't the end of the world, because this guy doesn't seem like
he was your person. And that's a blessing when that relationship doesn't
end, even though it feels awful. So just give yourself time to grief and then
also be there for your dad. I gotta be honest. I don't think you're upset
about the breakup. I think you're upset that he dumped you before you dumped
him. You think? I really don't believe I
really don't want to believe. That's true. Based on there's, like, a little bit of
a bitter tone to the email, which I never use that in a negative way.
I love it. I condone it. Tedious. I love it.
People say, oh, you're better. You go, oh, because I'm a woman in the world?
Yes. So, yeah, I think that's
why. Because you gave all this to
him and it still wasn't enough. And then he says
this fucking gut wrenching thing to you, which is like, you don't feel like home.
So to me, it just really feels like you aren't a good match.
24 and 30 can be a
little rough depending on where he is emotionally, because 24 is
just so young and even like
and, you know, again, the things I learned the hard way 2022 things
I learned the hard way. Being emotional and being emotionally intelligent are
two different things, actually. People who are really emotional
in life have lower emotional intelligence than people who
are kind of stoic. And I read that in a book. Is that
crazy? Because people who are overly emotional don't
know how to censor their
own emotions, which is a part of being a functional person in the world.
I know. It is really, really interesting stuff. It is. You know,
actually, you gotta get a grip on yourself. Am very emotionally intelligent, but I am
not very emotional. And I think a lot of people will be like, a clin
doesn't have emotions. I do. I just keep them inside where they belong,
hidden. But yeah, so I
think that's part of it, I gotta say, like,
because from my breakups now in retrospect,
going back, the Frank one, I don't even think about that
because I was just mad that I got dumped. He wasn't a good match for
me. The minute he found the woman he's now married to, I knew
I said, that's the fit. I said, oh, you found her. I was kind of
excited for him. I was like, you found her. Good for you that it wasn't
me. And that sucks because I wanted to be I want everyone I want me
to be everyone's soulmate and then me to only have one soulmate. But that's just
a dream I have. I don't see why that's reasonable. I want
everyone to be in love with me for the rest of their lives and lose
sleep at night. But I only have one true person for me when I find
them all now. But I really think that
the two much harder breakups for me were James
and Dylan. The ones that I initiated. I didn't want to
initiate them, though. I didn't want to initiate them. You gotta do
what you gotta do. You want someone to come back and give you more.
Sometimes love isn't enough. You want someone to give you another chance.
You want all these things.
And then that's how you start to feel like, oh, wow, I'm really not special.
I'm just like a slot that's being filled and it sucks.
And you cry, cry, cry, and then you're like, is this how life is?
And then Kritin and Mike are like, yup. But I really do have to
say I think your dad's cancer arrived at the serendipitous
time. And it's a weird thing thing to say, but I think this is going
to help you reassess a lot of things in your life. And like, what does
a 24 year old love more than how to make her dad's cancer about her?
Yeah, this is a time to like and also there might be a part of
your mind that it's so painful to deal with the fact that your dad has
cancer that you're like, instead of focusing
on the heartbreak of the breakup, because I'll do that too. I was really
sad about one thing, and then I was like, I can't be sad about this
thing anymore, but I couldn't not be sad, so I just chose
another thing to be sad about, and it really did work. I don't think
that's a healthy response, but it works in the moment.
Healthy schmalthy. Well, it's toxic to be sad about something,
which I totally understand. Yeah. You want to revert the energy somewhere else because you
got the feelings in you. You got to come out somehow and just truly,
like, give yourself a lot of humor during this time.
And it felt it's so vindicating to be reading
the Buddhist book When Things Fall Apart, and they name humor
as one of the three most important things in life,
because did I make a joke about Aaron Carter's death?
And I kind of feel bad about it? Yes. But I also, like,
truly sad and cried over his death also. That but
it's like, those two things can coexist, and I think it's
important. I made jokes that made people
around me go when my dad was dying and, like, still on.
I love them. Like, no one gets it, you know, unless you also have a
similar sense of humor. But if Buddha says
I'm right, then I guess I'm just doing it right?
So kind of Pemma was like, Great job, Corn.
Now back to my Buddha reviews. Yeah. Can't argue with Buddha. Yeah,
there's a lot going on right now here, but I just don't think part of
the issue is that you love this guy and really mess them. I just don't
think it's true how the fuck you told us this in the email. I mean,
I got to be honest. I get the ick when someone
says they don't love me anymore. And it is wild
to me how other people don't get the ick
when that is said to them. There's no way that somebody
doesn't feel a twin when that's said to them. There's no way. I like,
one's immune to that. I lose. What do you mean? Like,
you're saying you get the ick when someone says they don't love you anymore.
That's common. No, the ick is like, I'm repulsed by their existence.
That's what the ick is. I see. The ick is what you call it when
you're been dating someone for six months and all of a sudden you don't like
the way they chew. Like a hard turn. My pussy
dries up so fast. So that's why
the Frank breakup hurt, because it was, like, in retrospect,
a blow to my ego and also
a realistic view on
how close you can be with someone and then how you can kind of meet
them the next day relationships,
am I right? But I was never like, man,
I want him back as
soon as he moved on to his wife. There was a little time there,
but as soon as I was like, oh, he's serious. Because I was like,
maybe he was just playing hard to get that. But when I
really moved on and found the person who he needs
to be with, I was like, oh, yeah, I'm not interested
in this person right at all. Right. Yeah.
IK. Ick. That's the. Ick. Got it.
Yeah. So I think those are things to and
I know you're very young. This is a huge thing
to go through. I don't know what's stage cancer. Hopefully it's treatable. But spend
a lot of time with your dad. Yeah. Never going to regret going and hanging
out with him about his life. I feel like a lot of us go through
our lives without knowing our parents well. So if you have a good relationship with
them, I would ask him about his childhood and make funny videos with him,
watch movies with him, all this stuff.
This is the time to do that,
guys. You can hear us in other places. Did you know that?
No. Well, we'll tell you about it. Actually, I did. Just kidding.
I have a patreon where I do solo episodes of
my solo cut podcast called The Voices in Our Heads. I put out at
least once one a month. And then I do group therapy over zoom.
And that's therapy and quotes Chad, because guess what? I'm not a licensed
therapist, but god damn, can I facilitate a group in talking about their
feelings? And it's been an incredible day in my
month. I really, really enjoy this. And if you want to sign up for it,
just do the five dollar a month level patreon.com.
Christinahutchinson and also I do all these fucking classes with Laurel and
Jackson and with shit about past lives and ghost shit. I explore all these topics.
I record those classes and I upload them onto my patreon. So there's a lot
of bang for your buck of just $5 a month. So patreon.com
Christine Hudsonson you won't regret it. And you
know where to find me if you want information on the news,
the comings and goings of world leaders
you're going to tune into without a country. It's on YouTube every
Saturday or anywhere you listen to podcasts. It is myself.
Mike Harrington is on the line a lot. It's a really great
show. And I am quiet quitting the
entertainment business. That being said, people love this
show so much. And I got so much positive feedback on it that I
actually was like, I'm going to keep doing it for the people. I enjoy doing
it too, for the people. I truly do enjoy it for herself. I truly enjoy
doing it. So if I could record it and then just upload
it to my room and then me and my dog could just listen to it.
That would be just as satisfactory to me, because it's the constant
fucking whining for a free show that I can't handle.
And that one's like free, free,
tough whining. But yeah, I appreciate all you guys
for listening. And it's a fun show, and especially going into the
midterm elections. And Trump is about to announce that he's running
again. It's supposed to be next week that he's going
to make that announcement. If you were bored with politics,
if you give yourself a little vacation, you need to listen again. You need
to listen again. And I sprinkle in some fun stuff. I sprinkle in a Taylor
Swift album review. I sprinkle in a little murder story.
I'm a fun gal. You can do it. It's fun. If you haven't rated
and reviewed Guys on the Apple podcast app,
be sure to do that. Click the plus sign and follow us. Give us a
rating and a review. We read them, we appreciate them, and it keeps us in
the top 200 comedy charts, where more people can discover the goodness that
is guys, we fucked. Going 500 plus episodes strong.
Also, guys, we fucked without the you. And thinking Mike,
guys, we fucked without the you. In fucked is the social media
handle for the podcast, where you can see us on YouTube, where we have
Dumbbechew, our and our stand up comedy special, our special day. You can follow us
on TikTok. Same handle instagram Twitter. Same fucking handle.
Guys, we fuck without the you and fucked. I'm at Christina Hutch.
I'm at Philanthropy Gal. And now on to the personal
part of the show. I just have something quick and light,
even though my heart is heavy. But for the first time,
I went to cheer on people for the New York City
Marathon. I've never done that. It's one of the best
fucking days of the year. I didn't realize how needed
it is for a bunch of people, especially New Yorkers, because we do everything
better to fucking cheer on a bunch of other
people just because they committed to a goal of running a
fucking marriage or going through a really bad breakup. Sure, whatever.
I don't give a fuck. There was no political divide. There was no no
gender divide, no racial. There was no divide. It was just
New Yorkers coming to cheer on. Like, some of the runners had
names printed on their shirts so we can go, OK,
Stacey. And I was just fucking clapping for people, telling them I
was proud of them. And it made my life so good.
There's a guy with a pineapple on his head. I saw. I saw. Yeah,
he rampized us. Okay. But also, I don't know if he did he did the
whole race like that. Did he do it because otherwise because
I was looking at his posture, I was like, that doesn't look like pineapple posture
to me. Well, there's a lot of up and down hill.
I mean, how he glued something. He had a
bald head. There's no way you can glue something as heavy as a pineapple in
your head. Was it a real pineapple? Maybe he cord it and then
it was actually either way, the idea pineapple.
You think it was a scam current. I don't even care. The fact that it
instilled a little bit of wonder in us and like, oh, my god, this guy
ran a whole fucking marathon with a pineapple on his head. That's so great.
People run in the marathon, saw in Spiderman costumes. There's people that were like,
obviously you have to take it seriously. It's a marathon.
It's such a worthy goal to have to set for yourself. And I'm seriously,
congratulations, everybody who ran it. People come from all over the world, and it was
so fun. Colin and I were just cheering. We made signs for people.
It was just planned to do this. Well, the day before,
he was like, oh, the marathon's happening. They go past your neighborhood, so let's do
it. Let's wake up early and do it. I'm like, yeah, I've never done it.
I can't believe it. He ran the marathon a couple times, and he was like
he's like, you will love this day just because of the
human spirit that is generated. And I'm like, oh, because I love the gay pride
parade was my favorite day of the year. Hell, yeah. It's been now second place
to the New York City Marathon because it is so
nutritional for your parent former ally. Christina.
It's my second favorite day. Sorry. It's my second favorite
LGBTQ residue. Because we're not celebrating someone's
sexuality. Because we're more than our fucking virtual celebrating our mental.
It's much better. We're just celebrating setting a fucking
goal for years. How long is it? Is it 36?
26. 26. But then also Dee pointed out a
shout out to Guerreros in her Instagram stories. She pointed out she
goes, I just found out there's over like $700,000
in prize money for the New York Marathon. Sure. She's like, I thought these people
were. Just most people are not
even close. To winning prize money. How many
people actually get money? Yes. So the elite runners
are doing it for fucking money because they look unprofessional.
Well, they start different. They're like, group one start now, and then ten
minutes later, group two. Yeah, because they can't have these idiots around them.
Yeah. I'm like, I do this for real? Yes. Fascinating.
And it was such a nice day. And it was such a nice reminder.
It feels good this year for someone running. That's it.
That's it. Life doesn't have to be so fucking complicated. We don't have to
relate every year. Christina, could I sell you on sports? No.
When you get into sports, it's the same thing. Basketball stuff.
But the thing is, there's so much corruption in sports. And like basketball that we're
not fucking the athletes up by giving them concussions and paying them millions of dollars
so they just have to fucking deal with it. And then, oh, you beat your
wife, but we'll forgive you. It's like, ugh, there's too much bullshit
with those sports. I hate to break it to you, but I'm sure rapists were
running yesterday for sure. But, like, for a moment in time, I didn't
wonder if they were a rape. I just wanted to clap for
them because they were fucking running. You could clap for
somebody because they're on the meds, which is.
I'm from fucking Philadelphia. We take sports way too seriously. If our
team wins, we destroy the city. Loses, we destroy the city.
I'm not really sports. And me, it's fine.
It's fun to cheer, for sure, but everyone
just gets wasted and then just fucking this was such
a pure day. This is such a pure oh,
my God. Yeah. Well, I think it's even amplified last year
when I was still living with roommates, one of my roommates ran the marathon.
And it's very fun, especially when you commit. Yeah. It's a huge
commitment to see them. Running by you're so proud of them. Give them water and
stuff. Yeah. It's wild how much it will lift your
spirits to just cheer for people you don't know. And you're like, I don't care
who you voted for. I don't care where you're from. I don't care how much
money you make. You're running. Go. Sarah.
I'm having a hard time, guys,
more than the marathon. But I'm trying not to wallow in it.
And I'm trying to look at the positive shit. And that's something that's positive.
Well, congratulations to anyone who ran in the marathon.
And congratulations to me because it was the first time when I didn't book
something on the Upper West Side. The day of the marathon. Paul and
I Paula and I have a gun hanging every time.
Fucking streak of making plans on the day of the
marathon. Right? Directly in the marathon, we will go
to Alice's Tea Cup every single time. And I
actually, Jacob's Pickles heard someone fucking talking on
Saturday. And I was like, don't make plans with Paula on Sunday. And it was
so funny. Paula had actually just texted me, make plans to make
plans. Holy shit. And I was like, what is it about us?
Energy marathons in the stars. Crazy. And I saw
her not that long ago. Anyway, all right, so are you
mine is not about the marathon. It is about well,
I have another marathon, marathon of life that women have to run.
The marathon of life. Yes. That we don't train for.
We just get thrown into it. Well, so I was just thinking and this is
based on events on the weekend, but like, this is something I had
put some thought into prior.
And it's about the currency of having a
boyfriend and. The value that we place on it in society.
Because I got to be honest,
when women get a boyfriend, and I am guilty of this too,
not necessarily, they act like they're better than you.
Society treats them with a higher value.
And it's interesting because I feel
this too. And that's, to me, one of the only perks
of having a boyfriend is like it's like, to me, it's like going out with
makeup on, like you feel treated better by society.
But I think this is really not true
and something that we have been convinced about and convinced ourselves about, because for me,
as an outsider looking in, I've never seen an accomplished
woman get a boyfriend and thought to myself,
wow, her appraised value just went up.
Never once have I thought that. But I
know when I have a boyfriend, there is something in my head better
than you that says, I know other people on top of right now.
Sorry, you're single bit. Yeah, sorry, you're sad bitch.
And it's a weird thing to think, because I certainly from being
me, I don't feel in my home that my value has gone
up. Oftentimes I feel like my value goes down because I'm not as productive,
I'm not trying as hard to look good because
I already tricked someone. Right.
I still try very hard and, like, a problem.
You didn't try hard. Like, you're five. Oh, right.
Too early. And so I don't give up,
like, two months. And I'm not that bold. I'm not
that bold.
I feel like me and most women,
when we have a boyfriend, we strut around like we're
wearing our final slinns, when in reality, it's the Emperor's
New Clothes. This bitch. I'm like looking at these women. I'll go,
you're pleased out, bitch. No, you look stupid
and it drives you crazy. Or, like, a more modern example
would be like, you ever see that video of Lord when she thinks she's,
like, dancing? Really good thing,
really bad. Yeah. I got to find that moment really a
choreographer so much more of a contribution to society when
a conversation has a boyfriend and is like, peacocking him.
You look like Lord dancing when she thought she
could dance. And we were all like, Holy shit, this bitch can't dance.
And it's embarrassing because Lord is one of the most talented vocalists and
songwriters living. But I really do I love Lord,
but, like, she's such a no bad dancer. When you say peacocking your
boyfriend, do you mean, like, on social media everywhere?
She's not showing up all the time. Being with
them, people are like, tableau functions. There's an
excited way that girlfriends will be around their boyfriend, and it's
like, only you're excited about him because he's bringing down your value,
everyone. And so I was in a place where that was happening this weekend,
and it was, like, hilarious to me.
Wow.
I was like, Am I in some kind of an alternate universe.
And I don't know, because I certainly understand the feeling. I try
not to do it in public, but I mean, on social media every now and
once and again, I'll do it constantly content.
But there is something where you do feel like,
oh, other people are going to notice me more,
or be like, wow. To seem as, like, posting a lot
about a TV show you're on or posting about how
much money makes, it's very, to me, very similar.
But it kind of only works with
straight women. I think it works in the lesbian community. So I'm just saying I
can't speak for them. It doesn't work for men, though. That's why
men keep the fact that they have a girlfriend away from the
world for as long as I think possible. So that bitches still dm'em on
Instagram party game I invented for myself. How do you do that? Was looking
back and forth at couples Instagrams and counting how many squares
the woman has dedicated to the guy on her main feed and how many
squares the man has dedicated to her.
But see, significant. Let's make a new role of song. Just don't post a buy
relationship on your Instagram. Crazy.
And taking it to even, like, the next level. The amount of times I've seen
a chick walking around with a guy I dumped and the look in
her face when she sees me, it was like I made a mistake.
I accidentally sold a treasure at a garage sale, and now she's about
to make millions on Antiques Roadshow. This look,
and I've seen it many, and they're giving me the evil eye because
they think I want this guy back. Vintage shoehorn. And I'm like,
Girl, I already bit him like this to see if he was gold.
And the gold plating came off on my teeth. Wow. Come on.
It's scrap metal. Like, you got a scrap metal boo. And then I
was also thinking about and I was like and I was like,
even a step further. The most notable thing about all
my exboyfriends, with the exception of two, was that they dated me.
Yeah, you're going to do that and then moving forward. I think the
most notable thing about some of you ladies is that
you fucked someone who dated me. Uh, if that's not going to keep
you up at night, haunt your dreams forever,
I don't know what is. That's it. I'm sad. I am me.
No one likes me, but I am me. And that's sad.
What a crazy, meaningless existence we have.
Just like, boyfriend is not currently. We get people
get really caught up in the comparing of all kinds,
comparing bodies, comparing relationships, comparing income status,
comparing careers, comparing everything. And I think we just need a
friendly reminder to take a step back and reach down in our
own Honey Pots and make our lives magical
and wonderful. But you have to boldly pursue that it's addicting to
compare yourself, and it's detrimental to your soul. Well,
beyond comparing, too. It's just like it's truly like this heterosexual
female notion that man equals currency. Right,
but that's why women tend to be so desperate to share the boyfriend
saying, because it's like, oh, you think that is way more value than it does.
I mean, there are times when it does. I mean, I think we see it
more in celebrities like Power Cups, david Beckham
and Victoria Beckham. Yes. That added value to both of their situations,
for sure. But I mean, that's how amazing you have
to get. That's how amazing you have to get. You have to be one of
the number one footballers in the world and one of the most famous pop stars
of all time with her own clothing and makeup brand. Like, that's what we're talking
about. And, like, when you say it's a call out, it kind of is,
but it can't be because this is
not even based on this has happened multiple times now.
Experience. Yes. The same exact scenario. So at this time, it's like,
this is not unique. This is a pattern that has been created or
that I am recognizing. And it's
sad. I had never heard a ton of people talk about it
before, but Clementine Ford talks about it a lot. She's this
wonderful Australian feminist who I'm absolutely obsessed with. Speaking of muff
diving, I'd love to, but she
just will go on these rants in her Instagram story, and everyone
is fucking feminist poetry. It's so good. Wow.
She added to my favorite. I just wish and people
have very polarizing opinions on her, but of course you do, because she's awesome.
If she was not awesome, people will be like, she's great, but she's awesome.
So people like, what a bitch. It's like, yeah, a bitch
with a lot of money, a lot of followers. She's wrote a lot of,
like, best selling books. But she's just yeah,
she was talking about it, and I was like, this is you really? And she
has a child that she made with a man, I'm guessing
probably. Somewhere along the line. Yeah.
And it's also part of it is like, I'm saying it out loud because I
also don't even know how to fully undo it within myself.
Because we always want to be of the utmost value. We want to be doing
all the best things, achieving all the things. And it's like,
how do we like knowing how we exist
on our own? Seeing the stats, seeing the statistics
about happiness, about finances, about success
levels that women experience when they fly solo.
But then how do we undo that need for this currency
that is voiced? It's the currency part, because I
think love is so it's a necessary part of
life is fucking lonely,
and it sucked most of the time, for sure. And I got to be honest,
it's nice to have someone by your side. Yes.
Until it turns into but that's also not
this conversation is about it's not like that love isn't good. Right. It's the
currency. It's about how other people perceive
you when you have a boyfriend, as if you have more value. Right. So it's
not about is your life periodically better or worse?
Right. Of course, sometimes it's not something I don't believe in love or, like,
relationship. No, not at all. It's just so funny that you bring this up because
from the male perspective, it is so different. Like,
not having a girlfriend as a man. I think when
you have a boyfriend, your boys would give you like, this bitch got. Yeah,
kind of. When I see my friends in relationships,
most of my close friends are in really good, happy relationships.
I'm happy for them in that regard, but there is a part of me that
is just like, man, oh, man, this is such a different life,
and I'm glad I'm not doing it right. Like, the relationship life.
Yeah, well, that'll downlife both,
I think. Because I think what I get from my friends that are
in relationships, some of them, the ones that are a little more mature, that have
kids and stuff like that, they look at me as they're just like,
oh, it'll happen for you. Somewhere you
got freedom. Yeah. What that's priceless? So it
is weird to me that they look at women
that don't have boyfriends as like lesser
than some sort. Of this is kind of like a
continuation of the piece that I wrote for I guess it was. Glamour magazine
when I was 30 and started dating James, and everyone fucking congratulated
me like I had just won the goddamn Nobel Prize, right? Anyone who knows him
knows he was not we had so many conversations about this topic on the
podcast, and it does like, somebody, a colleague was engaged. Like, I found
out she was engaged the other day at the comedy club. But I was.
I said congratulations. And then as I said it, I was like,
what am I really congratulating her for? I just want I don't know.
I love when people find love and she's great. Yes. But I'm like,
oh, God, I wanted to be mindful that I'm not I still
say things like, congratulations whenever people have a baby on purpose
or get married. You're still like a human existing
in a society with certain structures.
And yes, it is exciting. And I think yeah,
it still deserves and I think it doesn't deserve a congratulations when someone gets engaged,
but it definitely does. But they
didn't make value go up. Right. And the energy that you're talking about, there's,
like a desperation, and it's coming from a place of bullshit.
It's coming from a place that's fake. And it's also
like, you know, I think it's like, okay, so we're all,
like, say every little thing in life has a
piece of value and, like, we're going up to try and make a hundred or
whatever. So it's like, yes, I think there maybe is some low value
in having a partner from the outside perspective.
But it's like, wouldn't she rather be,
like, blondie? She never got married.
But would I rather be unmarried blondie or would I rather be
a married lady blondie?
Blondie like Debbie Harry? Yes. Or is
she married? Or would you rather be like Victoria Beckham?
I think well, that's different. I mean, Victoria Beckham,
that's like fourleaf
clover. That's why we talk about it so much,
because it's like, how many actual people can you name who
are both equally powerful, equally good looking,
still love each other after all the time, raise their family by themselves
and didn't have, like, higher nannies and shit?
She had nannies. No, she's not as primary caretaker. That was,
like, a big thing for her. Wow. Yeah, that was, like, a big part.
I'm pretty sure Debbie Harry on that list of people.
There's, like, a list of women who have never got married and
are like and it's like when you look at the list, you're like, this is
like everyone on this list is a fucking banger. Yeah. Just an incredible
list of people, right? I knew she was involved with one of the guitar players
from no, Not Married. It's not that these people don't have
relationships. It's not that they don't believe in love. It's not that they never even
cohabitated none of putting all your eggs in the relationship basket
is just valued by society. But it's stupid.
It's so funny to see. It's really funny
to see, especially someone with
someone else that you used to date.
You launching it in your face, like, I didn't already live
that life. I don't actually know what's really going
on behind the scenes when someone brags to you about
something that you don't give a fuck about. That's one of the funniest
scenarios that life has a fuck. It's just like,
I know the truth, right? But they think they have
all this value and you're like, no, you don't. What the
vision of somebody in front of you going, ha ha. Karin. And you're like,
Sit on it. I don't give a fuck. Like, your problem now, bitch. Well,
and the funniest thing is, all the people who have experienced with, like, the man
in every single instance, his life got significantly worse when
I broke up with him. So it's like, you're flying
a lower value item than I once had in my face.
Right? It's like, you should go ahead and have them. You live in a van,
you shit. On a diamond ring. And then you're just like, don't you
wish you had this diamond ring? I'm like, It smells like poop. Can you leave?
Get your poop ring out of my home. Get your poop ring out of here.
We're joking and stuff. But it really did leave me kind of, like,
left a real sadness in my heart, because as much as I love to troll
bitches,
I want every woman, every woman, even women
I don't particularly like or respect, to want better
shit for themselves.
What are you doing? That's our Christmas wish. What are you doing?
Oh, God. Every goddamn time.
So should you take next year off to cheer for people of the marathon
yesterday to clean my apartment since I was Alfred? That's nice.
It's salad. That's great. Which I know sounds sad, but I fucking love salad.
I, like, literally, like, green salads, dog time salads. That's fucking
that sounds wonderful. I love the crunch of the iceberg lettuce. Okay,
guys, our guest, we love the crunch of his comedy and his presence
on our show. Look out for his one man show coming up called
my dad isn't Danny DeVito. You can also watch his YouTube stand up
comedy special for free called Brain Noise. Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome to the show Anthony DeVito.
And then I'll just use so we don't have another interest, but we'll just
do. The only thing we'll need is this last email. Okay?
Do you want to do the ads now, or do you want to wait?
Can we wait? Yeah, because I always fuck up my rhythm a little bit.
I just have to pee really quick.