Whose fault was the wool panel? It's November and I want to wear my clothes.
We can't even see your bottoms. I looked at
the temperature. I knew it was going to be warm. Yeah, I think you,
like, complaining or something. I should have not worn
them. Yes. There we go.
Burn from our wound. Behind the scenes. This is who we are.
Yeah, this is behind the scenes. I just hate the heat.
So god, too much.
What a fucker ty you doing? How you been? We're happy you're here.
Welcome to another episode of Guys We Fuck. It's the anti Slut Shame
podcast with a sweaty meatball over here. Because we're in camera
sweaty. I'm Christina Hudson. We can take you off camera. That'll solve
that.
Wow. We see people's true intentions. Shiny.
Oh, my God. My spicy meatball.
Oh, I've got.
That might be true. You can't let me know what makes it sad. I don't
think women are going to. Care that you said that. No. My God.
Anyway, welcome to the show. We're happy you're here. If you want
to email us, it's sorry about last night's show@gmail.com.
Today's subject line, I don't want to fuck my husband because
he will not shut up about not getting fucked. I have
been there hey. As old as time. Hey, ladies, I'll get
straight to it. My husband will not stop joking about how we weren't
going to have sex anyway. Oh, my God. Are you dating my ex
in response to everything I do? Oh, Jesus Christ. That's kind of
funny. I just had a baby four months ago.
Wow. Slow down, partner. Anyone who talked
about this on an expert level as far as babies
and stuff, they will say, expect not to have sex for a
year. Oh, really? Than a year? Yeah. I mean, also, too let the
person that just popped a baby out of their hooha fucking
rest if they want to. That's what I say. If you've been in a relationship
long enough, what's the difference? This should be all
that to you. My friend of comedy. Back in the stand up mike,
that's spiraling. What heat will do
to a man too high literal heat. I just had a baby four months ago
and it's been a rough journey, to say the least. With PPD
PPA trying to kill me, I have to work incredibly hard just
to keep from drowning. Oh, so much stress.
Yeah. No one wants to fuck under that. After an entire day of working
from home while also caring for the baby, I'm fucking spent.
Yeah, girl, I'm spent for you. He gets home and sees me pumping and
goes, wow, I haven't seen those in a while. Oh, I would kill him.
Show this to your husband. I would kill him. Fuck you, buddy.
I'm putting my middle finger up. Show this to him. Yes.
Brent taking his dick off. And that's me going, oh, fuck yourself.
Oh, actually, sorry. She'S now
mining a tinier dick. She gave him too much leeway. She pulled a real
maze, put him on a pedestal, crab after an entire day.
Okay, after work, pumping from home,
caring for the baby. I'm fucking spent. Yes, I'm pumping. And he says, Well,
I haven't seen those in a while. Or we'll make some other ogling comment.
God, he has no game. How did you have a baby in the first place?
That makes me want to crawl out of my skin. I cannot exist
around him without being sexual, and it makes me physically ill.
Although it may sound like I don't hate my
husband. Haha. Oh, my God. My sex
drive immediately say that for the court record. My sex drive
immediately dropped after I got pregnant, and I've been basically
been disgusted by sex ever since. All the comments on
top really solidify the grossness I feel.
When I talked to him about it, he said, quote, my brain is just
processing it like this. Even when I tell him that it hurts
me and it makes me not want to have sex.
The childbirth you didn't go through made you an asshole.
My brain is processing it like this, sarcastically.
Yeah. Without putting any physical labor into it for my body.
Are all men just so incredibly incompetent?
I'm going to say no, but my glass is always full. Girl. Does he not
care that he's hurting? Not helping. I'm reading the
book Come as You Are to try and tackle some of my processing about sex,
but so far I think I'm just fed up. I mean, I'm fed up with
them and I don't even fucking know him. I'm only 26,
so this is particularly everyone just cried a little bit. We all
got so sad. This had the weight of a 38 year old email.
Reds. Yeah. God damn. I'm only 26,
so this is particularly frustrating because I feel like I'm too young to already be
this miserable. I gotta be saying, you hate men a lot.
I don't blame you of it, but yeah, I went through this for how young
you are, and I know you don't hate your husband,
but we do. I'm also a bit late on the dumb bitch train.
By 25, I've already carried my husband to his dream job
while living in suburban Hill and starting a family just to realize I've completely
thrown myself away to achieve this. God, I hope your kid doesn't say this big
yikes. I do love being a mother. I'm getting so sad.
But it really sucks to realize everything I gave up without actually
being able to comprehend the decisions I was making while I
was young. This is why we do the work that we do.
We will. Girls, boys days and thems, everybody,
don't fucking get married and don't get married before 25. Just don't.
I would say the good news is, though, you already have a baby and like,
you're still so young that you still have so much.
Not that bad. Yeah, you're a young mom. That's pretty dope. I wanted
to mention this because I'm sure it has to do with my lack of interest,
but I'm not sure how to move forward. I don't want to hate my husband.
I really don't. But I don't know what to do at this point.
Thanks. PS. Love the special. Look, girl, not every
man is like this. And the fact he's your fucking partner.
He's your partner. He is raising this kid with you.
He needs to be utterly respectful of where
you are at sexually four months after you've
popped out a baby, whether it's through your vagina or through cesarean section.
And this motherfucker has makes remarks when you're breastfeeding,
when you're pumping. Tell them to go to hell. Don't tell them that, but tell
them I said it. That's so fucking inconsiderate. I think you can tell them to
go to hell. It's so fucking inconsiderate. That is so inconsiderate
of what your body has been through emotionally and physically
and mentally. That is insane to me. You're really going
to have to let him know that this is fucking serious, that he's not respecting
your boundaries and throwing these little one off lines of I guess we'll never
have sex. Are you fucking kiddingmate? You know what that does to a person?
It slowly chips away at you. What are you, my mom?
Don't you got to have a serious conversation about he needs to knock this the
fuck off and you're not fucking around. Also, like,
making a joke and like it
I'd honestly rather have someone be like, hey, you stupid bitch,
fuck me, then make a little side remark
about how they haven't seen my boogies. Like, it's so
immature. It's so immature. Also, it's fucking gross. That is not a man to me.
That is not sexy. He's acting like an immature boy. How could you want
to fuck him when he's acting like your son? Well, the fan is like,
they're so young. I'm guessing perhaps maybe they are like a similar
age, you know? Right. And like, he's a 25, 26 year
old man, but still, like, I've met 25 26 year old men
that can have respect for the fact that their fucking wife just gave
birth. But who do you know who's 25 I'm married? I was like, I don't
know about you. No, I was like, it's all
men that are not because the
comments this to me feels so 25 like, the comments because
it's like they're not you're going to just have to need some of the choice.
They're like, not in a place where they cannot take not getting
fucked, not personally.
And so probably not only enough to. Have a kid, but.
On their end. But yeah. He just does not understand the
complexity of your mental
health situation, your physical situation,
and you're really trying hard to meet him
in the middle and meet him where he's at, but I think he needs to
do some changing. Yeah, I think I don't know
the extent at which you've talked to him, but you have to have like a
very serious sit down conversation. This will not fly about postpartum,
about the physicality, about what childbirth is.
Get him some pamphlets, get him a book, get him some YouTube videos.
Also, he better. No, he better. There'll be
a quiz. Say there will be a quiz and give him a quiz in two
weeks. He also needs to understand, because he clearly doesn't because if the goal is
sex, he's not going about it in a way that is sexy.
Your body and mind not being ready aside, when the point comes
that you are ready to have sex again, he needs to understand that these fucking
one off remarks are so mature. That is the biggest fucking turn off.
It is the biggest fuck, oh my God, I'm turned off for you.
He has a four month old child. Spend time with your child. I'm sure there's,
I would guess, 1000 things to do around the house right now.
Yeah, it probably is. Yeah. I know it's hard, but I'm
not going to be like, leave him. No, it's not great for you. Yeah.
And if he's young right? Also if he's young, we're still malleable.
These are the things in a relationship that we got to communicate. It turns
you off when he does this and that's something that he needs to know.
And I think, sadly, age aside, this is a rather a
more common experience that women have than they would like. And obviously I'm
sure a lot of women don't talk about it because it's kind of like embarrassing.
And I just went through birth well, and also going back to the conversation
that we were having about the currency of boyfriend, or you can call it the
currency of husband, same thing. We oftentimes
make our as women, we make our heterosexual relationships
sound better to other women than they actually are because that increases
the value of the currency because we don't want to be embedded there.
We don't want to be embarrassed.
I think this is a really common experience.
We heard a similar email on Dan Savage at Five podcasts.
And I think just like, the reason why people aren't talking
about it is because it's embarrassing. Because we don't want other women to
know that we have a husband at home who's like, not completing
the fairy tale. And I think we finally did start
to talk about it. And that's why we all had this AHA moment
universally where we're like, wow. We were all sitting at home
silently unhappy, because we all thought that we
were all experiencing these relationships in the movies that we
see in the movies and it was only our husband or our boys, and that
was fucking up. And that's not true. And that's how men got away with murder,
both literal and metaphorical. Murder for
fucking years. Yep. It's not happening anymore.
Anymore. So we got to have conversations, because that's how people grow and change,
and that's how you can be closer to your husband. He needs
to understand what you need right now,
and it's not him. They have it in them. They have it
in them. Saying they don't is giving them another excuse.
Exactly. And I think this talking point of
men being incompetent they're not
you're not incompetent. They weren't incompetent. Secretary.
They weren't incompetent. They wanted to build an app. They weren't competent. They wanted
to put together their fucking Two K team challenge. Now it's
getting personal.
You gotta stop it. It wasn't
personal when you wanted to edit the video of you on your vacation.
But what I wanted to do is of our vacation. Okay, now it's getting really
personal. Two K is a basketball. Two K is a video game.
That was the thing where we walked by and there was a whole crowd at
Skin Fest, and you were like, what are they doing? Are they playing video games
like they're playing Two K because they haven't grown up? That was that.
Come on. It's a little easy. Shut up. All right, Michael, enough from you.
We don't want to hear from a man right now. We're a little sensitive to
your gender downfalls and
excuses, frankly.
Communication is key. Communication is key. It's the last thing
we end up we want to do for some reason. But I tell you,
you got to do it. You scrambled your DNA together. There's a human
being that exists that's half you have him. We gotta work this out, baby girl.
And just a men listening. Who if you want to have kids with a woman,
I mean, just fuck it. Don't try to know what you're getting into. Dick your
dick into that bloody gaping hole until it's healed. Unless you want it.
Maybe she wants it. Yeah, well, some women, when they're pregnant, their horny is fuck.
And they're like, I've never been to Horny. And then the guys like, oh,
my God. You know, it's pheromones and hormones and stuff. And then some
women are pregnant, they're like, don't even fucking look at me. And that's fine,
too. Everybody reacts to the surge of hormones and what's happening in their body completely
different. Literally creating a mini you.
Yeah. Respect that, please. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You don't
go what you want. Build a bear and mushroom stamp one of the guys who's
helping you stuff the arm. You could, but you get a rest. Be respectful.
Be respectful. So I don't dis someone the same as you. Don't go to
a restaurant and then call the waiter who's about to bring out your food a
stupid client because they're going to spin your food. That's true.
Thank you so much. Wow. Or just an food. Okay.
Yeah. I was like, that visuals only for if you watch it on Youtube.com.
Yeah, we actually do special visuals for YouTube. So if you
want to see our hand gestures, you don't have to go to the YouTube version.
A lot of fake. Jacket off. Jacket off Youtube.com,
guys'bugs, without the you and fuck that's. Also, our social media handles Facebook,
Instagram, TikTok, Twitter. I'm at Christina Hutch. I'm at Philanthropy L.
Were you at Mike? I'm at Mike Cascarelli. Yay. You can also
see sometimes someone be talking, and then you can just tell them just, like,
processing of something really big in my head while they're going through it.
Yeah, so watch that on YouTube. That's fun. Just go,
what was I thinking of that in that moment? Yeah, very interesting.
Yeah. Sometimes I listen to the show and I
obviously forgot what I said, but then I'll respond in the same exact way
that I ended up doing it on a show, and I was like, wow,
you are very much yourselves. I'm jealous. It's like a hilarious game. I'm so
jealous of you.
Do you listen to the show and kind of know what you're going to respond
with? There was a period where I would listen to the show and get so
embarrassed because I kept interrupting everyone. And looking
back, I was like, the worst mental health period of my life. But I thought
it was the adderall. No,
it was like crazy anxiety and crazy, like,
just depression and me trying to be like, It's okay. All right.
That's what it was. Fueling it. And then I'm just like, oh, wow. I really
and then people emailed us about it, and I'm like, oh, I want to die.
I want to die. But you know what? I can only go up from here.
It turns out I can go lower.
Now you're finally understanding Mike and I'm religion over here,
nihilism limbo. Things can always be worse.
Oh, you're at rock bottom. Get a shovel up.
Challenge accepted. Gosh, baby.
Oh, my gosh. And also, you can find us and listen
to us at other places. You guys. I have a patreon where I release episodes
of my solo podcast of Voices in Our Heads. And I have
three to four times a month, I have Zoom Group
in quotes, chad Therapy. I'm not a licensed therapist, but I facilitate this
group therapy that I really fucking enjoy for an hour a couple of times
a month. So $5 a month will get you that, and that's pretty
cool. And also access to, like, all the weird classes I take.
I record audio and I upload it. Is that legal? I don't fucking know.
You know, I'm just fucked up. I doubt it. I paid for the fucking ticket.
I paid for the ticket, and now I want my patrons to enjoy it.
So patreon. Comcastinatchinson.
And then you can listen to without a country. It's my political podcast.
It is on YouTube. Without a country podcast,
we talk about the news. We talk about the most important news stories of the
week. It's mostly cover American news because we're doing it from the perspective of
the right and the left. But we also do a ted bit of international
we have a lot of Australian listeners, which I find to be very interesting,
and Canadian listeners. And we talk about animal rights
and we talk about pop culture. It's a great show. It kind of just like,
gives you a wrap up of what happened in the week so you can have
a conversation at the workplace and not seem like a fucking idiot. But you don't
have to, like, read all the news. Like, we kind of skim it and find
out the most important stuff for you. And we make jokes and it's fun.
So, yeah, listen to that. And it's also available in pure audio anywhere
you listen to podcasts, including Luminary, Apple, Spotify, all the places.
How are you? I'm good. We're just recording two interviews
at once. So we have to pretend that we had two weeks of life.
But I did store things on my phone. I scrolled across
an article. I have subscribed to Apple News. And I was like, I think this
is one of those articles where only two people said this, but they're trying to
make a headline to piss people off. But it was like Taylor Swift going on
tour in 2023. I want to move my wedding date. I'm like you fucking
what? Wow. What? Wow what?
Just go see her somewhere else. Yeah, but you
know, it's your prerogative. And you know what I do. I'm such a fan of,
like, having fun. But it's going to be hard to get.
I mean, I couldn't even get Lewis Capaldi tickets.
He sold out all his shows in like 2 seconds. And he's not as big
in the US. So he was only playing Radio City Musical here. I mean,
listen, I'll get it, but it's going to cost me a fucking fortune to get
the ticket off of StubHub or whatever. Does anyone have a CCA?
I don't know. He has like some fucking Scottish representation
or something. I should look it up. Does anybody work for Louis Capali? Can you
get current tickets? Give me a phone number.
Tell him I looked him up. Our compatibility on the pattern app. And the pattern
says me like it, uhoh if
he doesn't run from that, maybe they are meant to be. Oh, he's very weird.
Okay. He's very weird and I like
him a lot. Nice. How are you? Good.
Have you ever okay, so have you ever gotten into
your therapist head where you got your therapist to think more like you?
That's a you thing. It was a real win for me. My therapist,
my bestie, literally was telling me that she was in a session with
another client and then it was a man.
This could be bad. No.
And he was like, my life was over.
And she started she started thinking of me and
all, like, these feminist ideals. That I pumped into her head.
Nice. And she was like, man, I really wish that Corinne was here.
And then she was like and she was like she
had the feminist response that I would agree with,
which was like, how about you, like, self sued for five fucking
seconds? But she was like, that. I had to get out of that mindset because
I needed to help him from where he was at and his
relationship with his female partner, because he basically
wasn't getting enough attention. And I was like, oh, wow. I love
everything that I'm hearing right now. I hate that. That's a problem. I feel like
I got too much into her head. And also another
proud of that. I think she thinks too highly of me.
So then she'll think, like, I'll give her scenarios and
she'll definitely things are. Going to work out. And I'm like, I honestly don't think
they are. I think you just think I'm so awesome.
Wow. Literally, at one point,
she said to me things like, she's not you. And I go,
Are we? I said, but are we in love? But are we in
love? Wow. And I go. I go.
Do I agree with you? Obviously. But is that the
way that the world actually works and functions in this advice going to
help me? I don't know what it is,
but. Does she help you in therapy? Honestly,
I'm just there to complain for an hour so that I don't have to complain
to someone I know in real life. Right. That's really all therapy
is for me. Yeah. No guiltfree.
Complaining every now and then. Every man should try it.
She'll recommend, like, a book or give
me a little line or something. That's helpful. But most of all,
it's just me airing my grievances, which make me have better relationships with the people
around me because I don't hold in the resentment. That's great. And then it's
like, let the air. Other than that,
it's like me working out a bit by talking it out at an open mic.
Ultimately, I'm coming to the conclusion by myself. We have very
different therapy sessions. And then sometimes, obviously, with things like, OCD,
she introduced me to tapping and stuff, which actually is very helpful. I'm like,
we'll meditate a little bit. You know, that kind of stuff is good. But yeah,
no, overall, she'll be like, you're great.
You're good enough. And I'm like, that was never an issue. What are we talking
about right now at SoulCycle in the Hamptons? Yes.
She'll be like, you are safe. I know. I'm in my house. I'm fine.
I don't need these kind of thought. Like things to say.
There'll be a quiet moment. And she'll be like, are you afraid that
everyone you love will leave you? And I go, no, obviously not.
Like, what? Just funny to me. I go, yeah, I never
even crossed my mind until you just brought it up right now.
It just makes me laugh. That's great. It's such an interesting insight
though. A therapist's response to me is such interesting insight
into what other people are going through. Because I
know, obviously it's a numbers game.
She's giving me the answer that's most likely to soothe me.
No one is an expert in anybody else, you know? Right.
And so when she gives me these answers and I'm sure soothing to many
other people, they're not. I'm like, wow, everyone's real fucked up.
Yeah, that's true. And they are real fucked up. And they are. Every day is
a struggle. I'm just like, that's just not and.
Then I'll just like, get off this zoom and I'll be like, well, at least
I'm not those other people that those responsible for.
True. So therapy didn't work in
the way that it was intended to, but it still worked, you know?
Gotta love therapy. It's funny to me. You know what's funny to me?
These guys, the interview you're about to fucking hear. Oh, my God,
you guys. Cran and I, we went to Skate Fest Las Vegas and
it was everything we thought it would be more. It was fucking fantastic.
I lost a lot of virginities. No. Whole virginia.
I was like, what? Aid Virginia and crowd surfing Virginia at the exact same
time? It was great. I feel like I had a laugh gasm.
It was awesome. But one of the other awesome things was the
live recordings of guys we fucked were fucking fire.
Okay, we're really excited to present you this first one. Ladies and
gentlemen, please welcome to the show karen Fehan
and Chloe LeBranche.
Hello. What an outfit. Karen sexy.
Thank you so much. Hello.
I was flipping. Hello. All right, take a seat.
Take a seat. Do you guys have any thoughts on the selection of
men that we've seen so far tonight? Could you tell? The wet spot
for my parents suffering back here.
And while you weren't a match so you could breathe.
Common buckets in my fish net.
Clean up and I don't care. Is it like, hard for you to.
Get wet or you get wet very quickly? I'm a real wet bitch. Yeah,
like all the time wet or something has to happen. Yeah. If you want to
feel it right now. Christina, I wish I was kidding.
What made you wet? It's not really a hot outfit.
I thought she was like, I love sunship. So that vending machine story just
really got me offending.
I didn't really come to the poor youth.
Well, this festival has plenty of that. Okay.
Chloe, are you what? I'm all dried
up.
Always wet in her brain.
Karen's wet in her mouth. I'm sucking all the dick today.
Can I say something about the rape stuff? Yeah, please. Not rape
if you have a job and.
No men. Listen, to that.
If you have a job. Yeah, I've been thinking that for years. Okay,
there's a guy in here who's, like, maybe that vending machine guy is hiring.
Carrying a blow job.
When was the last time you gave a blowjob? You like that?
Oh, my God. All day today. Wait,
wait. I think she got so many spots.
Chloe came here booked on one show. She's headlining
all day, guys. I mean, my office is in my. Mouth, so I'm
headlining back at the. Hotel, and there
is no HR, just age rape.
Okay, so Karen and I were talking about this before we started.
How many guys we go down the line. How many guys at this festival have
you each fucked? Me? Have I
fucked? Yeah. Zero. Wait,
we're not talking about, like, this weekend. So,
in the totality of your comedy court, no one here that you fucked? They're not
physically here, but they're on the roster.
They didn't show up because they knew I was coming. You scared
them. Got it. I mean, would I fuck a certain guy here?
Yeah. Well, yes. All right.
Does his name rhyme with pain? Lilith?
No, it rhymes with Danish.
Now. Yeah. I didn't know. How? Common knowledge is
Ryan Rayner how much Chloe wants
to fuck Gilly.
Oh, and keep don't forget about that,
too. I got three holes. Who's coming for the
next? Oh, yeah.
I got three. Wow. This has all been a joke.
Sign an NDA, please.
My puzzle is a fortress, and I'll
trap you in it'd. Only be what
is it when someone goes into your fortress?
Invaders. Rape. Yeah,
unless there's a job and their. Name rhymes with Philly.
What? Syphilis.
Okay.
You'Re probably here. Karen, how many guys have you
here? I don't know. Probably, like, a baker's
does or something. Wow. Really? What about weekend
two? Week two?
Yeah. I can't even think of Eddie. Oh, I can think of wine.
We flew in the porn star. No, I know that. When I thought of him,
the other one that I was like, I want. To have sex with you so
that. I can forget about this other guy that I really like. But you're also
cute, but I'm like. I don't know who that is. Okay, sorry.
Can you tell me, too? Oh, right. I forgot. You it's
here. Okay. Jim Norton. Oh.
Yeah. That guy could easily rape because he's a fighter.
Oh, the guy I whisker not Jim. Not Jim Norton. It's not a fighter.
Chim Norton will lay down and let me take it. Love that
man. Corinne. I'm sorry. I'm counting.
I keep forgetting. Okay. I wish I was more
of a slut analyt.
Wait, I got to redo mine. Okay,
mine is four, but three are comic. One's, not a comic.
And I also had one who it would be fine
if one person who was on the roster showed up. They're on your roster.
It benefits to figure out which one. Of the lucky volunteers, it was
blind Mike. Only so he can't
meet who you. Wait, there's a blind guy here? Yeah, he works here. He's part
of the guest digital team. Yeah, surprisingly, it's my dream to date a
blind guy. No. I knew that my choices in dating had gotten too sloppy
when I walked into gas digital one day and Blind Mike screamed at me,
she's mine. And I was like, I've been fucking too low on
the totem pole for quite some time. You want to date a blind guy?
Is that because they're good with their hands? Possibly.
It's just because I don't have to look. Yeah, you never have to wear makeup.
I don't think care about how I look. What a relaxing lifestyle that sounds
like. This is how blind people shake hands. That's okay.
You can touch my face. That's fine. Yeah. If you're blind, you could touch my
face. If you're blind and we're fucking, you could touch my face.
Has any one of these people ever fucked anyone with a disability?
Just Lewis. He's got
a couple. He has
Ad, Dhpv.
How is Louis in bed? Great.
You, like, hate fucking? Like, I mean, it always
feels that way when someone's sweating on you and talking about their mom under their
breath.
I'm kidding.
On my head. It's playing on my head. Sorry.
Just went all over you. Oh, my God. This stuff was so uncomfortable.
Okay. I haven't you
haven't what? The guy with a disability. Oh,
you should. But I wouldn't fuck a guy in a wheelchair because he couldn't get
away from me. You're mine forever.
Try to roll away. That's your horror
movie. You're just fucking collecting.
You don't have to leave. I got a closet of legs.
You're like Jeffrey Dahmer, but, like, waist down. Yeah,
except for I don't recycle because I don't eat the bodies.
You calling me fat, you bitch.
Yeah, let's give her Chloe fat. She won't make it to next game.
No one calls fat. Oh, my God. I don't think anyone
on stage besides me has actually been called fat. So keep doing it.
I like it. Or I called a hot retard yesterday.
Yeah. Someone goes, I didn't know autistic
girls could be hot. That's how they brought me up
on stage. Wow, a comics.
That better, because I didn't know his name. Yeah,
well, I brought him up and I introduced him, and I didn't know his name.
And then after, he just started calling me a hot retard, and I was like,
I'll fucking take it. Yeah. Because I blacked out. It up to the hot
compliment, right? Yeah.
There was a cleanup and aisle Chloe.
She made a mess. All right. This is
beautiful. She makes a mess. Okay.
All right. So I think it's like a grocery store.
We got the aisle reference at the grocery
store. We got it. We didn't think it was, like, an island in your apartment.
We got it. Sorry. I'm just used to my jokes not hitting friends.
Yeah, that's why I can't play blackjack here.
To remind you of my ex used to hit me.
Oh, come on, you guys. She deserved it. Look at her. Yeah.
Did you look at them just like that?
Sorry. No, I did deserve
it because there's a lot been a lot of cleanups in that house.
I get so wet and when a guy hits me
let's do a segment. I know everyone's powering. Yeah.
I'm really sorry about that.
But you got hit and you liked it. Hey, you like what you like?
Sometimes I accidentally masturbated after watching Woodstock
99 documentary. Sometimes we get off to
things that we don't like and someone else masturbated to that
documentary. When it's a guy, I'm not as impressed.
What's the weirdest thing you've ever masturbated to, Karen?
Why'd? You be so dead of the eyes.
Oh, God. You're probably just like a toxic ex or
something. Nothing that crazy. Oh, you know what? I used to have this reoccurring dream
that Lindsay Lohan beat me with a fresh fruit
platter and that got me kind of horny. She got big titties.
She does. She has her in.
They were in. It was the beating that I went because
she dated an ex boyfriend of mine. So I thought it was hot that she
was so angry. Have you ever masturbated anything weird, Karen?
Oh, yeah. Just like the kitty stuff. You're not supposed to say.
The kids stuff. No,
I just like really old guys. How old?
Like, you guys are the blue pill, man. Fuck you,
nerds. Oh, you mean the guys. You need
guys that are like gangbang, like a cheerleader or whatever? Yeah.
Like what? Like 75 at odds.
Might need a pacemaker change, right?
Yes. It's kind of hot. Will you die? I do that.
Any doctor exam? Porn? Yeah.
Have you parked a guy that old in real life? No.
How old did you go? I mean, going young, late, it's how my fault they're
like me. Yeah. When I was like
20, I fucked like a 33 year old for a while. This like, Israeli mob
guy.
Sorry. What's the oldest you fuck? 39.
How old were you at the time? 32.
That's not bad. And he was my boyfriend. I think if you said ten,
it would be really sold it. But I did recently fucked
a 25 year old guy. Named his name Jacob.
Jacob. Money mo problem.
What happened to Jacquemo? I was hearing about him alder in Cobet.
He moved back to Milano.
All right, but first before he moved to Milano, he was like, no.
So he dumped you and then he moved to Milan. But you like to say
that it ended because he moved back to Milan. He couldn't handle my trauma in
the bedroom. Right? How does your trauma play out in the bedroom?
And I choked. Jocko mo. And then he said, Stop,
I'm normal.
When you choke, you ask first. You just do it. Why would I ask?
Because then it could be a no.
The rapist applause.
Do you ask before you joke a guy? I don't. It's caused
problems. No,
I'm not gay. I guess, you know,
genders aren't a thing anymore, Karen. No. It's all lucid,
baby. Yeah. So women can choke first now?
Yeah. Put that on your Hinge profile.
I choke first and I'm a comedian.
Anybody have fucking quote? He's a life alert. Zero matches.
Okay. That was hilarious. I thought, though,
too. Thank you. I'm going to come to that later.
Okay. It's come to the time when
we need a couple more volunteers on stage. These also
should be men. Another loan stakes like that.
How not to rape, I promise. They're probably leaving.
We got some voluntary.
All right. Hi. Tell me more. Do we well,
we can do three. People more come up. Thanks.
That works. That guy just got up and he said, okay, I'll do it.
Hey, you guys. They listen. This is probably the easiest
segment that we have on the show. Yes, truly. And there is a
prize. There is a prize. There's always a prize. Okay, so this one is
very simple. You guys will introduce themselves. We have four, but that's
numbers aren't a thing. As Game Festival,
we're like three and like, we'll do four. I know what they
mean. They did four. They said three, but they need four.
You're fucking women. And all
you have to do is you're going to go down the table and you're going
to compliment each one of us on something that you
can't see. Okay. And if you've seen
it on Reddit, don't compliment that either.
But not aesthetic. That is a good point. But yeah,
it can't be like a part of it can't be like because Karen's wearing a
bra, you compliment her. Just so I'm clear.
Yeah. You seem to already keep it or. Something that I know about you
that I like. It has to be a quality.
A quality. It's not visual. Yeah.
TikTok with this one. So before I start, I was here a
year ago in Houston. That's when I met you guys. I got into
this whole podcast. So I really enjoy your guys'work. Thank you so
much. Well, you're already in first place, so thank you. No worries.
And the condos is over. What's your name?
I'm Joe. I'm here with my buddy Tommy.
We're both sailors in the Navy.
Now I know why you.
One by one first. This is my first time meeting you.
Thanks.
A very good quality that I see about you is that you're clearly on something
right now, and I love it. No, I'm actually sober.
She's trying hard to be sober. Actually.
Don't take that as a reason to do something later. Please quote retard
over here.
This is so accurate.
Holy shit. Holy shit.
Christina? Yes. I saw your set yesterday, and your
rape joke was the best rape joke I've ever heard. Oh, my god. Thank you
so much. An easy compliment. Okay. Not a joke in this
room.
This is going to be a challenging one. Inflection in that.
Okay. I was very surprised and impressed that you
own your own business with a baseball
card. Yeah, my dad died. Hey, what? Started mine
last year. We're in the same bucket.
And finally again, first time meeting
karen. Totally. I forgot what we're doing.
So sorry. I am ready to welcome your compliment.
Thank you. I would say out of the four panelists here,
you have the best sense of humor.
Comes out of nowhere and starts beating him up.
Thank you for participating. Thank you. That was a good one. You fell for the
old pitting women against each other. He will fall
for it. Thank you. Catfight on the LSV.
All right. That's number two. Matt. Matt. Okay.
Hello. Another matt. All right. You may go now.
Okay. Am I supposed to be calling all. Of you or just
can't be that hard.
The other guy. Three nice compliments in one
mean just like the other guy.
You better get your compliments.
Will we break our sobriety? I don't know who's getting chloe.
I love how you manage to take your trauma
and turn into so much charities. You think these are so
bad. Okay.
Oh, god. I really,
really love your story that you did on this is not
happening. About the jealousy that you were battling with.
I'm sure everyone can relate to that. Thank you.
The hesitancy before me every time. I know what to say to
you. No, I love you on master
show and I really enjoyed you every time you're allegiance tanks
and something no one's ever said before.
I enjoy it very much. And then
karen. Yes.
I like karen. I don't really give a shit about what everyone
thinks about me attitude.
How do you feel?
It was kind of a joke that this would be hard and now to see
how actually challenging it is,
it gets proven itself hurtful to us. Right.
We really walked in our own chat.
There's like five minutes like,
hey, we're going to put this in. You shouldn't need five minutes for one thing.
You can pass the mic. Thank you for participating.
Number four. Hi. Hello. Hi. How are you doing? Good. How are you?
Chilling. I'm good. Nice voice.
Now, what's your name? Phil. Phil, you made compliment
is hard. I was thinking the whole time.
From start fill. Okay.
It can't be anything I see with my eyes. Just saying. I know. That's the
challenge. Exactly.
You could do something with your eyes. No, that's not the rules.
That's the whole point of the challenge. We might have to do a follow up
segment so that could keep going alive for sunday.
I think you're all very funny. First of all, you can't do a group compliment.
No group compliment you have to choose who's the funniest.
The other three will just kill ourselves. Yeah.
Do you want blood on your mouth? Like dear Phil. Thanks,
asshole. I like your voice.
Thank you. Something you can hear. All right,
well, I can't see your voice. I like your
curly hair. I don't know if that's visual.
Feel my curly hair. My hair didn't touch your heart.
He was so proud of himself cause he didn't say tits.
He thought that was going to be a win. I like your show. Your show
is cool. Which one? This one.
Jesus Christ. All right. Are you really trying,
or I think. It'S been on the spot or whatever.
I don't know. You've been standing in line so he
has time to think. Yeah.
I had a carnival. He's like, I didn't know this first wheel went up.
I wish you asked me, how do I not rape questions.
Okay, corinne, how do you not rape her?
I don't. What? I just don't.
None. I felt her fault somehow. Now I'm
offended. I don't know what to say, cause. It'S the wrong segment.
You know? Go again on something
you can't see. Go again.
Compliment. The compliment. You know, the challenge. No, we switched
the insults mid game. Just forget her.
I think you're very quick witted, and you come
up with stuff on the. Spot really well, so yeah. Quick witted?
Yeah. Wow.
You have the same qualities. Thank you. No, I don't.
Well, men fall for stuff, too. That's so funny.
Okay. Go ahead, Karen. Okay. I like the Valenciaga.
See, you're representing people of color right now. Be better.
I'm white. Are you? No, I'm like oh. I was like,
Jesus Christ. My LASIK is inspired. Okay.
Holy shit. You scared me, Phil.
Karen, I love every time you're on the Realized podcast.
I think you're funny as fuck. Thanks, Matt. A really good one. Thanks, Phil.
Not Pat, but all right. Thank you. At least you remembered
that. He's never going to forget you now. All right,
what's your name? Josh. Josh. What do you do for a living, Josh?
I'm a comedian. But really, what do you do for a living?
Okay. It's really smart. I have a 60 year old fucking
roommate. Like that one guy's girlfriend. Are you fucking him? I'm trying.
Wow. For rent money? Yeah.
Got to do something for home.
I'm going to start on that end. Karen, I love your bank account.
I love your bank account. Did you give him money? I don't know.
He can smell it, too. Yeah, he's fucking
vulnerable. Corinne without
a country is one of my favorite podcasts that my ex wife used to make
me listen to. Wow. It was a compliment first, and then
what? A roller coaster of compliments. Cannot get past
something without a loaded compliment. I love it.
You're the better host, everyone. I've been a
host the whole time. But you've had other co hosts, and you've been the best
one. Okay. Thank you. Why'd you
and your ex white break.
I don't want to get into that. You brought it up. I know.
I did.
Show in Vegas. That's what happens when you make Chloe wait for her compliment.
Christina, I think you're really good at
cutting down men. Oh, my God. Thank you. You're welcome.
That's a good one. And, Chloe, you're the funniest one up here.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Clean up, banana.
Thanks, dude. I really needed that.
Okay. All right, we just had a little meeting
over here and we decided that none of you win.
Thank you for participating, though. This segment was for us. You may take a seat.
Thank you so much. I think the homeless guy won.
Yeah, for sure, baby.
A for effort. Wood. All right.
Who are you talking about? Almost got wood.
Yeah. No idea. I got that part. Okay, well, you have
a home. You probably fuck pretty good. Yeah. Have you ever fucked a homeless
guy? Kinda elaborate.
I met this guy in reab named Tommy who was addicted to crack.
And we had sex a lot, but he
didn't sleep much, so I didn't have to share the bed with
rehab? No. After, because he was on crack.
He went right back to crack when he yeah.
I find a stable life with you.
No, I drove him back to crack.
Wait. Oh, that's a great question. So how many people have
turned to drugs after you robot? Well,
mom and dad. Now they're divorced.
Santa Claus. Santa Claus. Hail says no.
I don't know. Probably him. Jockamo someone
that rhymes with Phyllis.
Bane. Phyllis. Okay. Garen bin.
That's it. Shut up. Did I talk to the girl?
Yeah. Really? Yeah. I feel like it was kind of. Rape,
but, uhoh was it? Yeah, because we were making all these
pina coladas, right? And the next day I was like, that was weird last night.
And she was like, Why? Mine were virgin.
I'm like where? I no longer am one. Oh, wow. Was it your
babysitter? No, it was this girl. I can't say who.
And she's really hot, you know,
like a ten, but it wasn't
for me. Lesbian sex or lesbian.
Yeah. Being gays. Not for me. Raped by a
woman? Yeah, it might be that part.
Have you attacked with a woman? Yeah. A lot.
Yeah. Damn. What about you, Gogo? I let
a woman finger me to save her marriage at a sex club.
Did it save her marriage? I think it might have saved her marriage,
but she had an acrylic on and it really hurt in my pussy.
But I felt like it was a mitzvah for a woman, you know? So it
was nice. But yeah, at one point I reached back just because
I was like, I'm not really enjoying this. And I didn't think she was either.
So I just reached back to feel if her vagina was wet. And it was
very dry.
Investigate. Have you ever talked to a woman yet? Just in college.
That's so basic. Yeah, that's so basic.
We were bartenders and I went to finger her and we stopped. I was like,
nobody's watching us. You're not doing it for attention
at this point. There's no point. No money.
Well, Karen, you've been making a shit ton of money on
only fans. Yeah.
How many people here are subscribed to Karen's? Only fans. Okay,
guys, so be a friend. You guys are full of fucking shit.
I see her pulling up an Uber VIP all the time. I've been to her
house. This was good. We're doing great work.
Yeah, the donations.
We've asked a lot of questions about your only vets because we're very impressed by
it. But can you give us some tips for people who wanted
to get into the sex work? Do you want to start the only fans here
you are not one competition. No, yeah, it's fine.
I mean, we can try to stick in the herd. Yeah.
The thing about only fans is like, the weirder you are, the better.
Like you don't know people's Google searches, right? Do you
have warts? Like really start showcasing them.
Really? Are you serious?
Not that I do, but if I feel
like this is a trick,
you bitch and I'm going to put you on a train.
You should be a pioneer, Karen. It's like the first guy you put handicapped porn
on, you're like earhart. She never came back. No,
but you shouldn't feel insurious about, like you're like
weird shit. You should feel good about it. That's the stuff that people are into.
I was going to do one for my feet. I was going to put googly
eyes on the toes. I was ruining it. I feel like I would be
pissed at me. If you like, maybe wrap those feet around a disc,
it might work. Yeah, right. No.
My dog has ruined but I don't know. I think it's cute. Like so many
videos. So what are you doing? Like writing? It'll be
like an India re song.
I'm glad it's just funny to you guys. But I'll be like,
bent over and then my dog will come in a frame and I'll be like,
not the dicks line out. I'll give you peanut butter later.
How many people are you into? Like silly like a silly sexual
encounter. Yeah, that's what I thought.
Okay, who's going to come skipping towards the rest? Me. I like better
than powder. I feel like,
baby, let's figure this out.
That's a big one. I mean, I wouldn't know,
but diaper. Play anybody who
sold her shit in. A tupperware for like five K. Yeah.
What the fuck? For free. A lot of money.
I've been just flushing that down the door. She owns two homes.
Wow. She's got way more baggage than that. Worth more,
too. Because I put it all in doggie bags.
The poop dumps like an elephant. That should be your
dump. Fuck an elephant. No, dumps like an elephant. Oh,
dumps like a that should be. Your only fanfree name.
You know, I don't know. They're getting a shot. I like that she was surprised
when she thought you said, dumb fucking elephant.
My mommy never told me that. Yeah, it's like Chloe the Great instead
of Catherine the Great. The way I died.
She got fucked by a horse and she died. Catherine the great.
Really? Yeah. Why is that like a party fact that
you have at the tip of your tongue? Did you see a video of it?
I'm really smart. Wait, did they
capture her and then let a horse fuck her? No,
she just didn't. She just wanted to do it. She was like the queen.
She was like, you guys hold our black eyes in the palace.
I got to get my size. I love that as a
party fat. Christina, do you have a party fat that used to impress suits?
You think I use that to impress?
I mean, I can start talking about. How aliens are real, and I start citing
evidence, and then I'm like, Where are you going?
They are, though I like to tell people bats have a belly button. I think
that's really cool thank you. Vibe right away.
Yeah. Well, you know what a funny thing is? I've had three separate boyfriends
give me taxidermy bats as a gift.
I've never had one taxidermy bat. I love all three
of them. The night sometimes killed a rat. Until right here.
Yes. Corinne, did you name them? No,
I didn't even I named my taxes. Jeremy Coyote, though. But not my bad what's
his name? Selena. It's after a Breaking Bad episode.
Karen.
Are you on shrooms right now? Are you
on Shrooms? I know. Are you in bonding?
This the
question is, do you have, like, a fun party fact that you use on
day to impress Tooth? I know. The god of partying.
It's Dionysis getting
all these other gods. He's the party god, right?
ISIS. Stupid. I thought you meant,
like, you were trying to join ISIS. You're already in it.
She's already getting into.
Happy. She is. She has a fucking vest on full of bonds. Wait,
so are you seeing shit right now? Obviously.
Thank you. All right, well, I think we've reached our
last interactive segment of the show.
There is a price for this, and this is the one where we're I mean,
depending on who you are and how you feel the most or the least of
you, I'm not really sure. Your emotional intelligence is so low. I can't really
gauge this. Nothing to do with
emotional intelligence. I think we have to tell them all
this. We can't just expect this of you. Okay, very respectful,
we do not tell. You what this segment is. Yeah, we have this
crazy idea just for really no reason in
a very low level prize that you
would come and show us your dick, only we'll
see it. No one in the audience will see it and review it, and we'll
review your dick.
And so the five components of criteria for this
dick review are and it's not necessarily the
best. It's just like, what we feel in the moment.
And you guys, according to our DMs. Y'All want to show us,
right? We're kind of
giving you this opportunity.
Let us look at you. Yeah, give us something. You know what I mean?
Show us your body. Bring us your decks.
I'm going to chop your head off because I'm an ISIS behind the
black curtain. Okay? So we will react to it, but. No one else will see
your day. So just know that show the
components are going to be girth length that'd.
Be soft or hard.
And then character, which I think is like the one that really is going
to give one of you a leg on this. Can you imagine fucking
a guy and then going, oh, that's your dad's character.
And then he cries and develops, has. A little bit of character there.
I can see it. All right.
He's apologiamadi of Venus.
Okay, thank you. No one here
has seen any character movies with I have
Big Fat Liar. Fat liar with Paul Giamatti.
Oh, okay. That's a Paul Gemati movie. Yeah.
He's like, can we play the movie?
I didn't know where to go from there. All right.
I'll give you a free subscription to my only fans. We have a volunteer.
Brave. Four dicks is a party. Here we go.
Let's go.
I don't actually know how to do that. We're going to make a really big
deal about the one that wins.
Okay, I have an idea. What if we put them in order of who we
think is the smallest? You don't
know. That's a good
gag. Quo literally a gag once
it gets to me. Unless it's
a carrot. Okay, let's go. All right, so we're going to have you stand
behind this one, right? The scrim. Well, I thought we were not going to sexually
assault the producer when you
guys go over to this one because there's other adults behind this one
running the show.
Okay, so this three guys do one at a time, unless you guys just want
to see each other's digs. Would it make you guys feel more comfortable if
you all showed us your Dixon unison and we went down the. Line and we
need to see them being used? No, we didn't say that.
We didn't say that. Anything Chloe says is a haha.
Okay. It's a little lol.
I want to get a good view. Me too. Everybody's, I'm going to come quote.
I was just walking closer. Okay. This is very exciting for me.
Okay. You are so right. I don't
even know what your name is. Wait.
Okay. Wow. That's a dick right there.
That's a good one. It's a dark tank. It's almost longer than
your ball. You're a thrower. Keep talking. It feels like it's getting
a little harder. Yeah.
Come on, show us how big.
It's a good boy. Okay. There's a red rocket.
Okay. We just start touching ourselves.
All right. I don't see a lot of those in ISIS, I'll tell you that
much. We're not allowed to wait.
What's your name? Ryan. Not the first time I've asked after
I've seen the deck. Okay Ryan. Next contestant.
Thank you. Congrats, Ryan.
I'm not telling you. You will show us your record.
No traumatizes a kid. He's like, I'll show you my dad. I'm not telling you
my fucking name.
It has, like, a spring to it. No helicopter.
Like a cat tail is the helicopter time.
He's a helicopter now. He keeps pulling
his underwear down lower. As a vet.
Yeah. You're trying to get character points. Okay. Thank you for showing us your
dig. I'm going to throw up.
No, because I'm dizzy from the helicopter. Okay,
got it. Thank you for showing us your dig. That was wonderful. Thank you so
much. Contestant. Yeah. I don't know why the fuck any of you agree to
this, but I feel like the line got longer. Okay, ready?
What? The line got longer. Let's see. What's your name?
Yeah. Okay.
He's doing the numbers aren't in your favor. That's doing it slow.
And he's, like, unbuckling his belt, and he's kind of doing like a
Vegas showboy move. Oh, my God.
Nothing has made me more uncomfortable than what set is doing. Me too.
Lift up the blouse. All right, Seth,
you got a z muscle and a dick and ball. Look at that dick right
there. Nicer body. Yours was a bit wider.
Wide balls. Very wide balls so far right
here. Ball width was it in the components, but we might have to add it
for Sad touch.
Don't shake hands with Sad. Okay. Don't congratulate
him on this. Yeah. Why does ball so far? Thank you,
Sad. We've seen it. Thank you very far.
All right. Running away from each other. All right. Come on
in. What's your name? More comfortable?
Dwayne. Oh, my God. Dwayne works here. I have parents for Dwayne.
Dwayne is am also. He works here. Is this going to
get us in trouble?
Okay. Dwayne is also touching it,
and he works here, so God knows where that hands going to go after Dwayne.
You have fraternal twin balls,
and I like that about you.
Karen. Are you seeing something to say other than that? What? We're seeing
how badly he wants to show her.
Happy trip, Karen. Happy. I like the way you rest your
hands right now. Just like, a little bit, like, three inches away from
the body on each side. You're kind of going back.
Dwayne's kind of like, nervous to do show and tell and preserve
babies. Yeah. His underwear and pants are
just here. And he's laughing so hard that. His deck is
moving like Joe Biden. Is looking for a handshake.
Like Santa's full of jelly belly.
What went through your head, Dwayne, when you were like, I work here, but I
should also show my dick.
What he's still showing us? Oh, he's showing us the path that says all
access. That feels so rape. Okay,
you can pull up it. We're also doing an added component of who
just had no inclination to pull up the pants after
showing it. Dwayne wins by a landslide.
Okay. All right. We can't have the audience. If you didn't see that's,
it give. Them a round of applause. That was wonderful being fearless. I honestly
can't believe we convinced you to yeah, I'm really impressed with you.
We have to both you just went back to their feet in shame,
right? Okay. We have to remember them. Yeah,
we have to remember them. Yeah, I remember it. Okay, so again, we're going
off girth, length, coloring, vinaige, and character like
vinaige. I didn't write that one down.
You didn't write down vinaig. Okay. I didn't see a lot of veins, but that's
because they were flaccid so far away. Yeah, also far away, but I'm
near sighted. I didn't see any veins. Yeah, I didn't see any veins. That's something
to do with your site.
Really good dicks, though, you guys. All of you. All right,
so if you guys can't remember the names, you can also vote by 1234.
Chloe, what are your thoughts? Oh,
I'm going to go with I
have a soft spot for Dwayne,
and I think we both share
the soft spot. Right. Get it. There are several
soft spots, so yeah. I'm going to go with
that. No, I'm going to go with Dwayne. I got to support the festival.
Yes. I also am going to go with Wayne, because he was the most excited
to show us and had his pants down the longest and was just the bravest.
So I'm going to go with Wayne. Yeah. I'm also going to go with Dwayne.
I don't know that he'll ever be voted in a dick contest,
so this is going to be his one opportunity where underdogs
flourish, it feels like if I don't vote for Dwayne no,
Karen, dwayne is already won, so this is
really just you. And I want to give a little festival award. Let me get
one more look at all of them. Second looks,
last looks, everybody back to show.
The winner has to show everyone their dicks. Yeah. They did not
agree to that. No, they don't. Chloe and your non rules.
Good prize. Wayne, get over here. Congratulations.
You won the dick competition and a free copy of Club Pink Sex,
but you can show us every day. Wait, can you go to the microphone for
a second? This is for me. Can you say, I'm Dwayne, whatever your last name
is, and I just won best dick at Skank Fest. I am Dwayne
Howard. I won the best dick at Skank Fest. Thank you.
You're hero. Dwayne. My fucking boy.
All right, guys. Thank you so much. That's been, guys? You fuck. Please give it
up for Karen, Feehan. And Chloe the Branch and all of.
The brave men who volunteered at
our show. We really appreciate it. I'm Christina Hutchinson. I'm corinne Fisher.
This has been. Guys, we fuck the anti slot shaming podcast. We'll talk to you
tomorrow for by. Give it up for them.
I just hate the heat. So got too much.